,full_text,hashtags,retweets,geo,tags
0,"Around the  country, millions of children live in dangerous conditions due to war, conflicts, disasters, displacement. 

They deserve a world where they can learn and play safely.

#Afghanistan 
#EducationForAll https://t.co/Yml3t8d79l","{'Afghanistan', 'EducationForAll'}",4,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
1,"Sneak peek! The #2019CPMS Summary just arrived from the printers! See you on FB Live on 15 Oct for the new #CPMS launch. For more info, check out the #FutureLinksInCP link at https://t.co/JmIBSviaAf https://t.co/rgGZ3J8uAq","{'FutureLinksInCP', 'CPMS', '2019CPMS'}",3,,[]
2,@TsarKastik @RT_com @JewRussophile they are usually very good at killing kids in Yemen.,set(),0,,"[('Yemen', 'LOCATION')]"
3,@FatihinFKM @TsarKastik @RT_com @JewRussophile See who’s talk 😂 are y the 🇺🇸 who destroys Iraq Afghanistan Vietnam killed &amp; displacement more then 2 millions ppl in Iraq?? More then a half is children? Who want to be look good ha!,set(),0,,"[('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Vietnam', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION')]"
4,"@CPiE_Global Thanks for this initiative , it can really change the life of children in Afghanistan and the rest of the world where children lives in more dangerous situation owing to conflicts , displacement and migration, There should be more attention paid for its proper implementation...",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
5,"Speaking of Afghanistan, conflict, terrorists, and children, documentary filmmaker Sharmeen Obaid-Chinoy spent a... http://t.co/Nx9NZbuf",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Sharmeen', 'PERSON'), ('Obaid-Chinoy', 'PERSON')]"
6,"An Entire Generation of Afghan Children Has Known Nothing But War: Save the Children 
#Afghanistan #War #Children #Taliban
Read more: https://t.co/A4wtjeNVZQ","{'War', 'Afghanistan', 'Taliban', 'Children'}",4,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
7,"Refugee children from Afghanistan play cricket near their host homes in Pakistan.
Over half of the world’s refugees are children. Many will spend their entire childhoods away from home, sometimes separated from their families.
Photography by Sebastian Rich for @refugees https://t.co/I3m2kbkTct",set(),8,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Sebastian', 'PERSON'), ('Rich', 'PERSON')]"
8,"In Afghanistan, childhoods are lost to war https://t.co/SxBTPTxnxU ""Children cannot develop critical thinking, which makes them vulnerable for exploitation by extremist groups."" @EzzatMehrdad https://t.co/xf8q7mXe8V",set(),2,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
9,"@sahraakarimi لا حول ولا قوه إلا بالله العلي العظيم،
We don't know which problem we solve first in Afghanistan 🇦🇫 :
War, children's rights, women's rights, education and health, which is incomplete. 🤔 🤔 🤔",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
10,"#Afghanistan is now the scene of the deadliest conflict on earth. Fighting continues to rage, exposing civilians, particularly women and children, to daily deadly risks, prompting mass displacement and choking the country’s unstable economy. https://t.co/kdgGGngw3S https://t.co/DvygDWQs5a",{'Afghanistan'},0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
11,"Every child has the right to protection and freedom from violence, but in Afghanistan, conflict is having a devastating impact on children https://t.co/dXrbyR1MMf

#ChildrenUnderAttack #NotATarget | @UNICEFAfg https://t.co/ahMgJFQevw","{'NotATarget', 'ChildrenUnderAttack'}",5,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
12,"په افغانستان کې هره ورځ ۹ ماشومانو ته مرګ و ژوبله اوړي- یونسیف
https://t.co/R8rXx3tHPa

#Afghanistan #ArianaNews #ATNNews #AfghanNews #AryanaNews #ATN #UNICEF #War #Children https://t.co/yQJ0n9bEz9","{'Afghanistan', 'ArianaNews', 'ATNNews', 'AfghanNews', 'War', 'AryanaNews', 'ATN', 'UNICEF', 'Children'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('ATN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UNICEF', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
13,"Every child has the right to protection and freedom from violence, but in #Afghanistan, conflict is having a devastating impact on children.

Learn more: https://t.co/8i6mP46OLp

v/@unicefrosa @unicefafg #ChildrenUnderAttack #NotATarget https://t.co/R0DDuJVNIi","{'NotATarget', 'Afghanistan', 'ChildrenUnderAttack'}",25,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
14,"Seen an ex BBC war correspondent asking for donations for “war children” victims in Iraq Afghanistan, Iran, Lybia , ... and the British had fuck all to do with the destruction of these countries?? Was that cunt blinded? He was there..what war was he reporting????",set(),0,,"[('BBC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('Lybia', 'LOCATION')]"
15,"Young Afghan peace activists amongst the winners! Congratulations!
#Afghanistan #peace #youth #war #children #refugee #migration #education https://t.co/BuG0R6fIVt","{'Afghanistan', 'education', 'refugee', 'war', 'peace', 'children', 'youth', 'migration'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
16,"Afghanistan is now the scene of the deadliest conflict on earth. Fighting continues to rage, exposing civilians, specially women &amp; children, to daily deadly risks, prompting mass displacement &amp; choking the country’s unstable economy. @Ian_Fraser @DickieMan
https://t.co/xJVZplcpID",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
17,Yesterday parliament voted against the right of refugee children to join their families. Merzia was separated from her family as they fled Afghanistan and this is how she remembers it. https://t.co/TiWKHNKmol,set(),227,,"[('Merzia', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
18,"Violence.
Displacement.
Drought.

Despite these barriers to learning, children in Afghanistan are grasping the opportunity to learn, and with it, finding a sense of normality in their lives.

UNICEF Afghanistan https://t.co/JW0ddYckXb",set(),1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('UNICEF', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
19,"Children are suffering from extreme malnutrition in Afghanistan. 

This is how UNICEF is supporting children in one of the world’s most lethal conflicts. 

#ChildrenUnderAttack #Afghanistan #Nutrition https://t.co/9kI0vQ0plz","{'Afghanistan', 'Nutrition', 'ChildrenUnderAttack'}",211,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('UNICEF', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
20,"Our Friends @UNICEF Reporting on EXTREME Malnutrition in Afghanistan Children because of Conflicts &amp; War.  
#children #childrenunderattack.","{'childrenunderattack', 'children'}",10,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
21,"@simona_poletti This is a huge problem not only in Afghanistan, but also in Libya and Iraq. Countries are in chaos and civil war. Children are victims of this. The most defenseless.",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Libya', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION')]"
22,"جنگ افغانستان در سال ۲۰۱۹ مرگبارترین جنگ برای کودکان در جهان بوده است
#Afghanistan #War #Children 
https://t.co/TtMoevw2Ii","{'War', 'Afghanistan', 'Children'}",1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
23,"A choir of refugee children from Afghanistan &amp; kids from Pakistan performed for @antonioguterres during the #RefugeeSummit in Islamabad, where he called for more youth empowerment and solidarity #WithRefugees. https://t.co/7uxIsVOLPc https://t.co/aFgRhdZpPG","{'WithRefugees', 'RefugeeSummit'}",133,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Islamabad', 'LOCATION')]"
24,"A choir of refugee children from Afghanistan &amp; kids from Pakistan performed for @antonioguterres during the #RefugeeSummit in Islamabad, where he called for more youth empowerment and solidarity #WithRefugees. 

🇺🇳 https://t.co/fYFzTuW012 @UN
#Youth2030 #SDGs #GlobalGoals https://t.co/h3bushUS9H","{'SDGs', 'GlobalGoals', 'Youth2030', 'RefugeeSummit', 'WithRefugees'}",6,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Islamabad', 'LOCATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
25,"A choir made up of refugee children from Afghanistan and children from Pakistan performed for Secretary-General @antonioguterres in Islamabad, Pakistan, on the side of the #RefugeeSummit on 40 Years of Hosting Afghan Refugees in Pakistan. @Refugees https://t.co/94wZaXKBk5",{'RefugeeSummit'},11,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Islamabad', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION')]"
26,"Former #USA drone operator recalls dropping a missile on #Afghanistan #Children and says military is ‘worse than the Nazis’

War...

Children are innocent victim but the target of US army &amp;  #Bush #Obama #Trump administration ...

https://t.co/gSnFOatpxF","{'Bush', 'Trump', 'Afghanistan', 'USA', 'Obama', 'Children'}",0,,"[('USA', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Nazis', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('Bush', 'PERSON'), ('Obama', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
27,"”Afghanistan är nu scen för den dödligaste konflikten på jorden” 

Afghanistan is now the scene of the deadliest conflict on earth. Fighting continues to rage, exposing civilians, particularly women and children, to daily deadly risks, prompting mass displacement and choking the",set(),4,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
28,"Violence in countries including Afghanistan, Central African Republic,South Sudan and Syria reported to result in 2018 displacement of nearly 31 million children;13 million refugees and more than 17 million internally displaced. (UNICEF 11/29/2019) #Zusia https://t.co/uKO8KEM1qV",{'Zusia'},1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Central', 'LOCATION'), ('African', 'LOCATION'), ('Republic', 'LOCATION'), ('South', 'LOCATION'), ('Sudan', 'LOCATION'), ('Syria', 'LOCATION'), ('UNICEF', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
29,"Just spoke to my friend MBS (Crown Prince) of Saudi Arabia, who spoke with President Putin of Russia, &amp; I expect &amp; hope that they will be cutting back approximately 10 Million Barrels, and maybe substantially more which, if it happens, will be GREAT for the oil &amp; gas industry!",set(),36422,,"[('Saudi', 'LOCATION'), ('Arabia', 'LOCATION'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'LOCATION')]"
30,@realDonaldTrump You’re friends with a murderer?,set(),938,,[]
31,@FrankFigliuzzi1 @realDonaldTrump See who’s talk 😂 are y the 🇺🇸 who destroys Iraq Afghanistan Vietnam killed &amp; displacement more then 2 millions ppl in Iraq?? More then a half is children? Who want to be look good ha!,set(),0,,"[('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Vietnam', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION')]"
32,@realDonaldTrump For America people who destroys Iraq Afghanistan Vietnam killed &amp; displacement more then 2 millions ppl in Iraq?? More then a half is children? Who want to be look good ha! #American,{'American'},0,,"[('America', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Vietnam', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION')]"
33,1/4 of the world's refugees come from #Afghanistan.Refugee children have been deprived of a home. But those back home tend to be worse off,{'Afghanistan'},0,,[]
34,"UNAMA report: More than 500 civilians killed, including +150 children, due to #Afghanistan conflict in Q1/2020, with a disturbing increase in violence in March. Urgent need for ceasefire. https://t.co/qa8B8NtGhJ",{'Afghanistan'},0,,"[('UNAMA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
35,"New UNAMA report: More than 500 civilians killed, including +150 children, due to #Afghanistan conflict in Q1/2020, with a disturbing increase in violence in March. Urgent need for ceasefire. https://t.co/1q2mN15LBg",{'Afghanistan'},2,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
36,"New UNAMA report: More than 500 civilians killed, including +150 children, due to #Afghanistan conflict in Q1/2020, with a disturbing increase in violence in March. Urgent need for ceasefire. Read more: https://t.co/9esFqbxPCb #HumanRights #ZeroCivilianCasualtiesNow https://t.co/mC0IK4xm48","{'Afghanistan', 'HumanRights', 'ZeroCivilianCasualtiesNow'}",66,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
37,"United Nations: 533 civilians killed in #Afghanistan conflict in Q1 2020. Anti-Government Elements (Taliban, ISKP &amp; other) responsible for 282 deaths (53%). Pro-Government Forces responsible for 198 deaths (37%). Read more: https://t.co/9esFqbxPCb. #ZeroCivilianCasualtiesNow https://t.co/SDl8Vw7fou","{'Afghanistan', 'ZeroCivilianCasualtiesNow'}",50,,"[('United', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nations', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
38,"New #UNAMA report: More than 500 civilians killed, including +150 children, due to #Afghanistan conflict in Q1/2020, with a disturbing increase in violence in March. Urgent need for ceasefire.  #ZeroCivilianCasualtiesNow https://t.co/LoO8Rav4cS","{'Afghanistan', 'ZeroCivilianCasualtiesNow', 'UNAMA'}",1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
39,"New UNAMA report: More than 500 civilians killed, including +150 children, due to #Afghanistan conflict in Q1/2020, with a disturbing increase in violence in March. Urgent need for #ceasefire. https://t.co/nqZNpqIs8V","{'Afghanistan', 'ceasefire'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
40,"More than 500 civilians killed in Afghanistan conflict in 2020: Report
More than 500 civilians, including more than 150 children, were killed due to the fighting in Afghanistan during the first quarter of 2020, according to a United Nations report.
https://t.co/LLaIRcvdIB",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('United', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nations', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
41,"New UNAMA report: More than 500 civilians killed, including +150 children, due to #Afghanistan conflict in Q1/2020, with a disturbing increase in violence in March. Urgent need for ceasefire. Read more: https://t.co/lfojBeIpPB #HumanRights #ZeroCivilianCasualtiesNow","{'Afghanistan', 'HumanRights', 'ZeroCivilianCasualtiesNow'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
42,"Afghanistan conflict still the world’s deadliest for children, UN says @starsandstripes #Afghanistan
https://t.co/qguj4k4PDC",{'Afghanistan'},1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
43,"Afghanistan conflict still the world's deadliest for children, UN says: Afghan children were also among the over 2,500 said to be detained for alleged or actual association with armed groups like the Islamic State. https://t.co/KppMW03lCU #islamicstate #islamicterrorism","{'islamicterrorism', 'islamicstate'}",2,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Islamic', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('State', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
44,Afghanistan conflict deadliest for children in 2019: UN https://t.co/MBacP2Ey3X #AFG,{'AFG'},2,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
45,"Afghanistan conflict still the world’s deadliest for children, UN says https://t.co/Ln8I2LSVky
#Childrenofwar 
#AfghanChildren","{'AfghanChildren', 'Childrenofwar'}",1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
46,"@birdiebidnest @MirMAKOfficial How you can prove this that he worked for western. All western and Americans, Jews propaganda, u believe that. He has no greed for money, why he will work for them? He belong to one of richest family of Saudi Arabia. Why he chose to live in mountains? He paid millions $ to PLMN.",set(),0,,"[('Saudi', 'LOCATION'), ('Arabia', 'LOCATION')]"
47,"@MuhamedAhsan @MirMAKOfficial He worked forWestern thats why he was living in the Mountains.He had left his homeland ,he was an Agent.Its done for Monarchy purpose not for money.American Troops and forces ENTERED Afghanistan in his name! killed thousands of children,caused Displacement of poor Afghan families",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
48,"Time to act now: Afghanistan’s displacement crisis is one of the largest and most protracted in UNHCR’s seven-decade history. We’re now seeing a third generation of Afghan children born in exile - @FilippoGrandi 
https://t.co/HteKVwjAqN",set(),6,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('UNHCR', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
49,Afghanistan’s displacement crisis is one of the largest and most protracted in @Refugees seven-decade history. We’re now seeing a third generation of Afghan children born in exile https://t.co/S7V7tC0HOl @refugees,set(),16,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
50,"They are responsible for the destruction,genocide,displacement of millions of women, children and men in:
• Congo
• Iran
• Iraq
• Panama
• Haiti
• Yugoslavia
• Afghanistan
• Venezuela
• Somalia
• Gaza
• Libya
• Syria
• Yemen
• Boko haram Nigeria 
• Ivory Coast https://t.co/UztwcxDDEm",set(),57,,"[('Congo', 'LOCATION'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Panama', 'LOCATION'), ('Haiti', 'LOCATION'), ('Yugoslavia', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Venezuela', 'LOCATION'), ('Somalia', 'LOCATION'), ('Gaza', 'LOCATION'), ('•', 'LOCATION'), ('Libya', 'LOCATION'), ('Syria', 'LOCATION'), ('Yemen', 'LOCATION'), ('Nigeria', 'LOCATION'), ('Ivory', 'LOCATION'), ('Coast', 'LOCATION')]"
51,"Conflict in #Afghanistan has already resulted in numerous civilian deaths, as well as casualties, with women and children on the front line, and displacement. Afghanistan🇦🇫 continues to be shaken by large-scale bloody #terrorist attacks, incl. in #Kabul. #FormulaArria #UNSC https://t.co/fHdl7vn8vP","{'Afghanistan', 'Kabul', 'UNSC', 'FormulaArria', 'terrorist'}",6,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Kabul', 'LOCATION'), ('UNSC', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
52,"Women &amp; children made up more than 40% of all civilian casualties in the Afghanistan conflict during first half of 2020.

New @UNAMAnews report calls on all parties to start peace talks, prioritize civilian protection, &amp; address needs &amp; rights of victims. https://t.co/pobD3bSE5g https://t.co/cf4VSRUE82",set(),99,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
53,"Agony of civilians in #Afghanistan never ends: death, injury, trauma, abduction, displacement, disease &amp; now Covid. Intra-Afghan negotiations are overdue, incl parties’ plans to invest in needs of women &amp; children; victims’ experience should be centrestaged @UNAMAnews @eu_eeas",{'Afghanistan'},4,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
54,"Here's the newly released @UNAMAnews mid-year report on the impact of the #Afghanistan conflict on civilians &amp; children.

Full report here: https://t.co/4VDs7qeYiu https://t.co/oE7mUtXyQO",{'Afghanistan'},2,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
55,"#KaradahProject and I are grateful for the generosity of those supporting displaced children in Afghanistan. Our kindergarten is giving hope to children displaced by war, poverty, and displacement.

Click. Contribute. Change the World.
https://t.co/ZgCnBwGbI8 https://t.co/MNflGtieaB",{'KaradahProject'},0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
56,"Hi new followers! Welcome to my page.

I'm an Iraq War Veteran and ER doctor on the frontlines of the coronavirus pandemic. I tweet about:
🔹deadly misinformation
🔹ways to mitigate spread
🔹lives lost to COVID
🔹school openings
🔹1918 influenza pandemic
https://t.co/fou6caoAhT",set(),802,,"[('Iraq', 'LOCATION')]"
57,"In a displacement camp in Afghanistan, education brings confidence and hope to children. 

Click. Contribute. Change the World.
https://t.co/CW8RHnMWIC https://t.co/VzarGPxONx",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
58,"In a displacement camp in Afghanistan, education brings confidence and hope to children. 

Click. Contribute. Change the World.
https://t.co/ZgCnBwGbI8 https://t.co/HqYShlHcls",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
59,"Joe Biden just announced that he will not agree to a Drug Test. Gee, I wonder why?",set(),84848,,"[('Joe', 'PERSON'), ('Biden', 'PERSON')]"
60,"Positive findings:

110% increase in women serving in national parliaments
38% decrease in maternal deaths 
18% increase in female literacy 

https://t.co/kgq2Y1Xt9j

#beijing25 #refugees #humanitarian","{'humanitarian', 'beijing25', 'refugees'}",0,,[]
61,"Persistent challenges:
Dramatic displacement increase: 26+ mil refugees in 2019; 13+ mil displaced women

43% girls in Nigeria subject to child marriage 

75% children in Congo &amp; 67% in Uganda w/o birth certificate

46% women in Afghanistan experience GBV

https://t.co/oOTTyUArkk",set(),0,,"[('Nigeria', 'LOCATION'), ('Congo', 'LOCATION'), ('Uganda', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
62,"Dr. Scott Atlas: 
These lockdowns are a luxury of the rich. The President understands that people need to work, the working-class need their jobs, children need to go to school, it's harmful to do otherwise. || #IngrahamAngle #Covid19 https://t.co/1VTOUHS2OQ","{'IngrahamAngle', 'Covid19'}",3791,,"[('Scott', 'PERSON'), ('Atlas', 'PERSON')]"
63,"Any Labour supporter saying #StarmerOut just please look at that thing in 10 Downing St that is our PM.

Unite and win.",{'StarmerOut'},106,,[]
64,Wow! The Afghanistan War has aged older than the Solider I lost during my last deployment. He was 19. #EndTheForeverWars,{'EndTheForeverWars'},2,,[]
65,"19 years since start of US war in Afghanistan:
- soldiers are now serving who are younger than this war
- children of war vets now serve w/ parents
- #ANDSF have grown, but suffer staggering casualties
- huge portion of land US troops bled &amp; died for is under Taliban control",{'ANDSF'},3,,"[('US', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
66,#WorldBank warns of increased #poverty in #Afghanistan due to #COVID19 shock https://t.co/EOQKK4zBdP,"{'WorldBank', 'poverty', 'Afghanistan', 'COVID19'}",0,,"[('WorldBank', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
67,Girls and women oppressed by the Taliban and denied education were deployed as propaganda to sell a war that the US has now lost. Millions of girls still have no school. Shame on every politician who promised to be the savior of Afghan girls. https://t.co/Wle4MykRZp,set(),103,,"[('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('US', 'LOCATION')]"
68,"Helmand has turned into a Taliban slaughter house tonight. Hiding behind civilians didn’t help them once our Commando units were dispatched. 
#Helmand https://t.co/Vtf6GzNpFP",{'Helmand'},7,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
69,"These people are being displaced from their homes because of the war. There are concerns about escalating clashes between the Afghan military and the Taliban.
Watch the chaotic situation of the families in this small video.
#Helmand 
#Lashkergah
#War
#Afghnistan
#SaveHelmand https://t.co/ukTsvdJyM8","{'Helmand', 'Lashkergah', 'Afghnistan', 'War', 'SaveHelmand'}",0,,"[('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
70,Countries guilty of human rights atrocities (eg in Xinjiang) should never be permitted to sit on the UN Human Rights Council. ⁦@RightsGAC⁩ ⁦@CHRDnet⁩ ⁦@UyghurProject⁩ ⁦@HRF⁩ ⁦@HRWcanada⁩ ⁦@chrlcg⁩ ⁦@UNHumanRights⁩  https://t.co/1GMSSoTms0,set(),18,,"[('Xinjiang', 'LOCATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Human', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Rights', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Council', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
71,Americans and Pakistanis make fun of Afghanistan to make themselves feel better but fail to recognize that they’re the ones responsible for the state Afghanistan is in.  besides.. your countries aren’t doing much better anyways lol,set(),14,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
72,Read our latest brief with @HelpAge on the impact of COVID-19 on Older Persons in #Afghanistan: https://t.co/Lbnfk0WSfA,{'Afghanistan'},1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
73,"#AfghanMigrant thrown off building by human traffickers in eastern #Turkey
 https://t.co/WMJaVZ7E5P via @duvarenglish","{'Turkey', 'AfghanMigrant'}",0,,"[('Turkey', 'LOCATION')]"
74,"Coronavirus means number of Afghans facing food shortages has risen by huge 5 million this year, according to new @WFP estimates. Some 12 million in 'severe food insecurity' at the start of 2020 and now more like 17 million https://t.co/34rRgiNbow",set(),30,,"[('WFP', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
75,"@AnahitMnats @VeneraArakelyan @KarapetGrigory1 @MesutOzil1088 You can read about #Khojaly genocide on many international sources. Also almost 20 countries recognize that. Let me underline that all of that are proven by photo, video and audio files. Do you confess that your country did that?",{'Khojaly'},0,,[]
76,President @realDonaldTrump has signed an executive order to form the One Trillion Trees Interagency Council to further the United States' contribution to the global effort! 🌳  https://t.co/j45YnVidWz,set(),5302,,"[('Interagency', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Council', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('United', 'LOCATION'), ('States', 'LOCATION')]"
77,"@Tasies @isawthesethings @johncusack @USNavy @Mike_Pence @JoeBiden Also, again, he's stepped up our unilateral involvement in conflicts in ME, SEA and Africa while simultaneously reducing the transparency we had into those activities. He more or less loaned troops to SA, ffs.",set(),0,,"[('Africa', 'LOCATION')]"
78,"@JaywalkingGuy @isawthesethings @johncusack @USNavy @Mike_Pence @JoeBiden ...put Venezuela on the exceptional threat list, Bush...well...Bush is responsible for the death of over a million civilians, destroyed Iraq, turned the mid-east into Jihadi central, decimated Afghanistan, backed a coup in Venezuela, also created a refugee crisis...",set(),0,,"[('Venezuela', 'LOCATION'), ('Bush', 'PERSON'), ('Bush', 'PERSON'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Venezuela', 'LOCATION')]"
79,#Jesuit Refugee Service/USA (@jrsusa) is deeply disappointed in the lowest ceiling in history of U.S. refugee resettlement. https://t.co/EdUyU4MGkE,{'Jesuit'},0,,"[('U.S.', 'LOCATION')]"
80,"@bayenciaga For leaving America. Go away. The only place they're ""tolerated"" anyway",set(),0,,"[('America', 'LOCATION')]"
81,A child born today won't know what it's like to live without a #lockdown unless they fight in the #AfghanistanWar,"{'AfghanistanWar', 'lockdown'}",0,,[]
82,"From a personal standpoint, it is a real sacrifice and an existential crisis to vote for someone who has killed civilians in Afghanistan and is so proud of it to name her book ""Shoot Like a Girl."" 
But what can one do!",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
83,"@nef__saaid but using the crisis in Afghanistan, which was created by the US, as a sarcastic joke??? Is so messed up",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('US', 'LOCATION')]"
84,"#Afghanistan's #Covid19 outbreak has pushed another 5 million people into food shortages:

WFP said the numbers deemed to be hit by “severe #foodinsecurity” had leapt from 12 million at the start of the year, to an estimated 17 million now.
https://t.co/NlwQUkzDL1","{'foodinsecurity', 'Afghanistan', 'Covid19'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('WFP', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
85,@Elohim_Gadol @realDonaldTrump He won’t kill people,set(),0,,[]
86,"There are now 80 million refugees in 2020 half of them children.
Photography Sebastian Rich/Magnum-Insights #afghanistan #refugeeswelcome #hope #NewYorkTimes #fujifilm https://t.co/VNT6Y7IYwA","{'afghanistan', 'hope', 'NewYorkTimes', 'fujifilm', 'refugeeswelcome'}",9,,[]
87,If you are anti-Iraq/Afghanistan war but support Joe Biden you are a hypocrite,set(),0,,"[('Joe', 'PERSON'), ('Biden', 'PERSON')]"
88,The 20th Year of the Afghanistan War Should Be America’s Last via ⁦@DefenseOne⁩  https://t.co/L3lQrrUwhZ,set(),0,,"[('America', 'LOCATION')]"
89,"Thinking #Afghanistan and #Hunger? 

Food shortages in Afghanistan as coronavirus worsens country's humanitarian crisis.
 https://t.co/HhNMOlkh4U","{'Afghanistan', 'Hunger'}",2,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
90,The 20th Year of the Afghanistan War Should Be America’s Last https://t.co/QaD2dsBupS @DefenseOneから,set(),0,,"[('America', 'LOCATION')]"
91,"“ #Venezuela is suffering the fourth-worst food crisis in the world, only behind war-torn countries like #Yemen, #Afghanistan, and the Democratic Republic of Congo” https://t.co/peEAzopnqr by @SabrinaMartinR","{'Venezuela', 'Afghanistan', 'Yemen'}",0,,"[('Venezuela', 'LOCATION'), ('Yemen', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Democratic', 'LOCATION'), ('Republic', 'LOCATION'), ('of', 'LOCATION'), ('Congo', 'LOCATION')]"
92,Afghan villagers fear militants’ return outside shadow of US forces https://t.co/gfD0x8Fsrv #World #Afghanistan #Conflict,"{'World', 'Afghanistan', 'Conflict'}",0,,"[('US', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
93,Iraq and Afghanistan War Veterans for @JoeBiden and @KamalaHarris !! #VoteHimOut,{'VoteHimOut'},0,,"[('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('JoeBiden', 'PERSON')]"
94,Telegraph - Food shortages in Afghanistan as coronavirus worsens country's humanitarian crisis https://t.co/LRHOcBSI4v #Afghanistan #AFG #coronavirus #COVID19 #FoodInsecurity,"{'AFG', 'Afghanistan', 'FoodInsecurity', 'coronavirus', 'COVID19'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
95,"#Libertarian leaning policies of @TeamJoe (@JoeBiden &amp; @KamalaHarris)! 🇺🇸

#LibertariansForJoeBiden 
1. Biden believes that LGBTQ+ people and same-sex couples should be able to build and protect their families. 

2. Eliminate the death penalty. 

Thread 1: no particular order...","{'Libertarian', 'LibertariansForJoeBiden'}",4,,"[('Biden', 'PERSON')]"
96,"Coronavirus means number of Afghans facing food shortages has risen by huge 5 million this year, according to new @WFP estimates. Some 12 million in 'severe food insecurity' at the start of 2020 and now more like 17 million https://t.co/YDjXBuf44H",set(),1,,"[('WFP', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
97,"#Afghanistan’s Covid-19 outbreak has pushed another five million people into food shortages, dramatically worsening the #humanitarian situation in a country already racked by conflict.
https://t.co/mMWIWo7JuI @WFP @WFP_Media @UNOCHA @ramya_ramaswami","{'humanitarian', 'Afghanistan'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('WFP', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UNOCHA', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
98,"Respectful discussion welcome! Or you can troll them. I've seen lots of Libertarians discussing Trump's ""possible"" Libertarian policies! Rand is really pushing ending the Afghanistan war. #Election2020",{'Election2020'},2,,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
99,"@sandyagoura @Elohim_Gadol @realDonaldTrump Yes he killed a lot of people in Iraq,Libya and Afghanistan. Biden and Obama created Isis or let it flourish in Syria and in Iraq which caused the deaths of hundreds of thousands of people. This nice old man who is a figurehead cost the displacement of millions of people.",set(),0,,"[('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Libya', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Obama', 'PERSON'), ('Isis', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Syria', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION')]"
100,"@kaanda_bataka @PissingGladiat1 @seemi_pasha After the disintegration of the Great Mongol Empire, a small breakaway faction known as ""Chagatai Khanate"" was formed whose kings claimed descent from royal Mongol line.

It was with this small Chagatai faction that Allauddin khilji waged wars. And every war was defensive.",set(),2,,"[('Chagatai', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Khanate', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chagatai', 'LOCATION'), ('Allauddin', 'PERSON')]"
101,"@kaanda_bataka @PissingGladiat1 @seemi_pasha Khiljis themselves were refugees who fled Afghanistan in the wake of Mongol conquests and found employment with Delhi Sultanate.

Throughout Khilji's reign, Chagatai Khanate held ancestral Khilji lands in Afghanistan and there was nothing Khilji could do about it",set(),3,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Delhi', 'LOCATION'), ('Sultanate', 'LOCATION'), ('Khilji', 'PERSON'), ('Chagatai', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Khanate', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Khilji', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Khilji', 'PERSON')]"
102,"@itshamix @AnahitMnats @VeneraArakelyan @KarapetGrigory1 @MesutOzil1088 Azeri media has published several photos of the earthquake in Turkey, refugees from Afghanistan, and massacres from Ex Yugoslavian war as proof of the Khojaly massacre.",set(),0,,"[('Turkey', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
103,"@M_Johnston1 @RightsGAC @CHRDnet @UyghurProject @HRF @HRWcanada @chrlcg @UNHumanRights You conveniently forgot the ""atrocities"" committed by US and its allies not long ago that bombed Libya, Syria, Iraq, Afghanistan, killed countless civilians, displaced over 3700mln refugees, gave rise to ISIL. XJ's training centre provides de-extreme &amp; job training 3-10 months pp",set(),0,,"[('HRF', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('Libya', 'LOCATION'), ('Syria', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('ISIL', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
104,Once upon a time. https://t.co/U39wrvP2OW,set(),3873,,[]
105,I just watched a Afghanistan war movie and the first person that piped up in my mind was MSG Anderson......the last time I spoke to him was when he called me after the first black female ranger graduated. Said I could do it and dude legit fell off the face of the Earth.,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('MSG', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Anderson', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Earth', 'LOCATION')]"
106,"UN teams working to assess humanitarian crisis in Helmand
#Helmand #UNAMA #Afghanistan #Taliban 

https://t.co/0xL3MXpcxx https://t.co/12LTQJexKC","{'Afghanistan', 'Taliban', 'Helmand', 'UNAMA'}",0,,"[('UN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
107,Taliban Endorse Trump and The Afghanistan War: The Cycle of Trump’s Fake Anti-Interventionism and Why We’re Still There – Tony Odarg https://t.co/k75mylpD8L,set(),0,,"[('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Endorse', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
108,"@terzininDefteri This room is one of over 30 meeting rooms at @UNGeneva. In a regular year we host over 10,000 meetings and conferences, large and small, looking into various issues, from human rights, to health, development, etc.",set(),0,,[]
109,"@UNGeneva @terzininDefteri 10,000 meetings just tell to word which issue solve like covid19 situation, syira, Afghanistan,Iran kashim, Iraq, refugees .",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION')]"
110,"Follow our series on #COVID-19's impact in #Afghanistan - after a brief on child returnees, we now focus on older people's wellbeing. We plan two 4-page briefs - one below and a forthcoming brief on #olderpeople caught in #displacement during the pandemic, with @HelpAge.","{'olderpeople', 'Afghanistan', 'COVID', 'displacement'}",1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
111,"Today, joint assessment teams are continuing to evaluate the humanitarian impact of fighting and displacement of thousands of people near Lashkargah city,  Southern  Afghanistan
https://t.co/35pMQzNrlT https://t.co/YsagtXWmXH",set(),4,,"[('Lashkargah', 'LOCATION'), ('city', 'LOCATION'), ('Southern', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
112,Thousands flee Taliban onslaught in southern Afghanistan https://t.co/O2We1u2NMd #World #Afghanistan #Conflict,"{'World', 'Afghanistan', 'Conflict'}",0,,"[('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
113,"More than 5,100 families or 30,000 people have fled the fighting so far. #FMTNews #Afghanistan #Taliban #Refugees  https://t.co/S06knhWoYn","{'Afghanistan', 'FMTNews', 'Taliban', 'Refugees'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
114,"More than 17 million people in Afghanistan, (or about half of the country), are experiencing severe food insecurity as the coronavirus pandemic depresses an already faltering economy. 
https://t.co/Pb69rfhzxB",set(),3,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
115,Food shortages in #Afghanistan as #coronavirus worsens country's humanitarian crisis @WFP  https://t.co/Wv328d8Wk8,"{'Afghanistan', 'coronavirus'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('WFP', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
116,"➡️Continued fighting resulted in civilian displacement and casualties in the south
➡️Casualties from IEDs in Laghman Province 
➡️1,897 people receive humanitarian aid from an NGO through AHF in the north

Read the full report:↘️https://t.co/MqDBnxRVnT https://t.co/QjFHZkyoKR",set(),4,,"[('Laghman', 'LOCATION'), ('Province', 'LOCATION'), ('AHF', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
117,This paragraph about camps is wrong and misleading. https://t.co/UrnhliL4su,set(),0,,[]
118,"#FactsMatter Lockdowns are a luxury of the rich. It is the working class and the poor whose lives are destroyed by prolonged lockdowns. Unconscionable and reckless to ignore that in order to naively focus on eliminating asymptomatic ""cases"".",{'FactsMatter'},4159,,[]
119,"@rain_later Here they specifically quote Pakistan - and they are wrong. As many as half (if not more) live outside what are called “refugee villages”. It also seems to conflate those who came due to Soviet invasion of Afghanistan in ‘79, versus those who came later.",set(),0,,"[('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
120,@invisibleme45 @GisiAnthony No he never was.. he was a CIA Operative.. a ghost.. created during the USSR vs. Afghanistan conflict in the 80s,set(),1,,"[('CIA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('USSR', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
121,Canadian soldiers were 20 minutes away from running out of ammo in Afghanistan War battle https://t.co/JKhuRwoxix,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
122,Canadian soldiers were 20 minutes away from running out of ammo in Afghanistan War battle https://t.co/8T3qwkevya,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
123,"Pakistan is surrounded by enemies that want to break off a piece and ingest it. Biggest among those are India, which NEVER accepted the 1947 partition and is still dreaming of Akhund Bharat, and Afghanistan the unfaithful. We fought their war, took its refugees. What did we get",set(),3,,"[('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('India', 'LOCATION'), ('Akhund', 'PERSON'), ('Bharat', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
124,"Update: The main trauma hospital in #LashkarGah continues to be at capacity with treating injured. The MSF-supported Boost Provincial Hospital is acting as an over-flow facility. Additional 20 patients admitted over 24 hrs. Total is now 40, including pregnant women and children.",{'LashkarGah'},18,,"[('Boost', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Provincial', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hospital', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
125,Canadian soldiers were 20 minutes away from running out of ammo in Afghanistan War battle https://t.co/U2a8MSM7x6,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
126,#Taliban in the area between Nawa and Nad Ali #Helmand #Afghanistan https://t.co/e1WKTiGN6f,"{'Afghanistan', 'Taliban', 'Helmand'}",1,,"[('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nawa', 'LOCATION'), ('Nad', 'LOCATION'), ('Ali', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
127,Canadian soldiers were 20 minutes away from running out of ammo in Afghanistan War battle https://t.co/sJuiVta15L,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
128,"Hundreds of refugees on the move amid total collapse of any authority in central #Helmand which is spreading further south. I think that #Taliban are making mistake by letting Sangorians free, because it will increase lawlessness and chaos #Afghanistan https://t.co/fqlQUna5KX","{'Afghanistan', 'Taliban', 'Helmand'}",0,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
129,😡 https://t.co/bAnwwq1nWN,set(),2189,,[]
130,"@SWAtlasHoover @DonaldJTrumpJr After 40 years of war, natural disasters &amp; persistent poverty, #COVID19 has thrown Afghanistan into an unprecedented health, social &amp; economic crisis. Despite challenges, people need humanitarian assistant  fund-raising for Afghan people Plesae 
 https://t.co/NdwFf9HMul lives. https://t.co/oh3YEArqK0",{'COVID19'},0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
131,perfect depiction of Tatas,set(),129,,[]
132,@upword_ Cat fish accounts are trying their best to reduce damage. 😂😂,set(),1,,[]
133,"Opinions wanted. Sound off if you are a Veteran of this 20 year war or currently serving (active, Guard, Reserves)...you have certainly earned the right to state your opinion.

The 20th Year of the Afghanistan War Should Be America…https://t.co/oiKZvD02DE https://t.co/Au8MbilNti",set(),0,,[]
134,"BREAKING NEWS: We’ve secured $55 million in #funding to help leading industrial companies around the world improve the reliability, resilience and efficiency of their #manufacturing operations through Machine Health. Learn more: https://t.co/6WrnGJSM6c https://t.co/8wbEXeiZem","{'manufacturing', 'funding'}",3,,"[('Machine', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Health', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
135,"Building a brighter 💡🔆 future for 150 families, more than 1,000 individuals, in Bamyan &amp; Daykundi
By installing solar panels they will have access to their own sustainable #energy 💡🔆 https://t.co/Yg5qmfq9sG",{'energy'},9,,"[('Bamyan', 'LOCATION')]"
136,@Amya2212 reality,set(),0,,[]
137,@UNHCRAfg @MoRRAfg @UNHCRAsia @unafghanistan @BurenCaroline @mfa_afghanistan @UNAMAnews @UNHCRgov @Refugees @IFreijsen @IndrikaRatwatte Please send as yours cantact thanks,set(),0,,[]
138,"@ajaeys Jim Sarbh , a Parsi spoke out against CAA which sought to give relief to unfortunate non Muslim refugees from Pakistan, Bangladesh &amp; Afghanistan
👇 https://t.co/FJm9czFoVL",set(),0,,"[('Jim', 'PERSON'), ('Sarbh', 'PERSON'), ('CAA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Bangladesh', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
139,"@ajaeys @Amya2212 Jim Sarbh , a Parsi spoke out against CAA which sought to give relief to unfortunate non Muslim refugees from Pakistan, Bangladesh &amp; Afghanistan
👇 https://t.co/P46GED6MkA",set(),0,,"[('Jim', 'PERSON'), ('Sarbh', 'PERSON'), ('CAA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Bangladesh', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
140,"@upword_ Jim Sarbh , a Parsi spoke out against CAA which sought to give relief to unfortunate non Muslim refugees from Pakistan, Bangladesh &amp; Afghanistan
👇 https://t.co/zu0EPVO5Xq",set(),0,,"[('Jim', 'PERSON'), ('Sarbh', 'PERSON'), ('CAA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Bangladesh', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
141,"In a new study, Harvard economist David Cutler &amp; Lawrence Summers put total economic costs of #COVID19 at $16T.

That's more than 2x the outlays ""for all the wars the US has fought since Sept. 11, 2001, including those in Afghanistan, Iraq, and Syria.""
https://t.co/aW9NJQF1Wa",{'COVID19'},25,,"[('Harvard', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('David', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Cutler', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('amp', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Lawrence', 'PERSON'), ('Summers', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Syria', 'LOCATION')]"
142,"@Half_Baaked @upword_ Jim Sarbh , a Parsi spoke out against CAA which sought to give relief to unfortunate non Muslim refugees from Pakistan, Bangladesh &amp; Afghanistan
👇 https://t.co/h7sL8j5JLM",set(),0,,"[('Jim', 'PERSON'), ('Sarbh', 'PERSON'), ('CAA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Bangladesh', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
143,"Conflicts have been raging in Afghanistan for almost 40 years, and the country has the third-highest number of refugees worldwide. Germany supports a project by @Johanniter to provide basic medical care in Gulan refugee camp: https://t.co/co6oe5weec",set(),10,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Germany', 'LOCATION'), ('Gulan', 'LOCATION')]"
144,I am fortunate to have a wonderfully close family but there are 225k older people across the UK who can go over a week without speaking to anyone. Please take the time to listen to others and #DonateYourWords… you never know what words you may get back! @CadburyUK @Age_UK https://t.co/Z7Vk9ryek8,{'DonateYourWords'},967,,"[('UK', 'LOCATION')]"
145,"Pakistanis don't make fun of Afghanistan to make themselves feel better. Pakistanis for decades graciously hosted Afghan refugees as brethren. 

Pakistanis are fed up of Afghan political aggression &amp; land grabbing ideas &amp; our political response is reasonable, expected &amp; measured.",set(),2,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
146,"@upword_ @Swamy39 was right,in calling Ratan Tata a hypocrite.",set(),0,,[]
147,The 20th Year of the Afghanistan War Should Be America’s Last https://t.co/ttTInSNvfT via @DefenseOne Just declare the war won and go home,set(),0,,"[('America', 'LOCATION')]"
148,"@Unaplohindu @upword_ @Swamy39 Jim Sarbh , a Parsi spoke out against CAA which sought to give relief to unfortunate non Muslim refugees from Pakistan, Bangladesh &amp; Afghanistan
👇 https://t.co/rbCiZAL5xw",set(),3,,"[('Jim', 'PERSON'), ('Sarbh', 'PERSON'), ('CAA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Bangladesh', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
149,"@captaintommoore @CadburyUK @age_uk After 40 years of war, natural disasters &amp; persistent poverty, #COVID19 has thrown Afghanistan into an unprecedented health, social &amp; economic crisis. Despite challenges, people need humanitarian assistant  fundraising for Afghan people PLz donate. https://t.co/VVAlsv6pMQ",{'COVID19'},0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
150,"Alarming: Thousands displaced by fighting in southern Afghanistan 
https://t.co/3A5qF21RRy",set(),2,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
151,"🇦🇫 Afghanistan:  This 40-year long cycle of death, destruction and displacement has to stop.  
https://t.co/3A5qF21RRy",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
152,"Thousands of Afghan families in vehicles with their belongings fleeing southern Helmand province on Monday to escape fighting between the Taliban and the government forces .The UN said Tuesday the conflict has killed or injured 200 people &amp; displaced about 35,000 from the area. https://t.co/dNpr5opwkh",set(),7,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
153,Why TF are we still in Afghanistan?! The Afghanistan war is a sophomore in college now,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
154,"More about (Rep) Charlie Wilson's War, funding the Afghanistan War &amp; Islamic troops on the ground, kicking Russia's (FN) ass! 
Even reagan recognized liked &amp; listened to him.
https://t.co/eS2Uw7lXnx",set(),0,,"[('Charlie', 'PERSON'), ('Wilson', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'LOCATION')]"
155,"“Thousands of people have been displaced and critical health services interrupted, after fighting erupted last weekend between security forces and Taliban fighters in the southern Afghan province of Helmand, the UN humanitarian office has reported.” 
https://t.co/ttvztDegtx",set(),0,,"[('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
156,"@rashedhashmi1 @kunalkamra88 Jim Sarbh , a Parsi spoke out against CAA which sought to give relief to poor,unfortunate, harassed, non Muslim refugees from Pakistan, Bangladesh &amp; Afghanistan
INDIA WILL NEVER EVER FORGET
👇 https://t.co/WKrsGa5uxT",set(),0,,"[('Jim', 'PERSON'), ('Sarbh', 'PERSON'), ('CAA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Bangladesh', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('INDIA', 'LOCATION')]"
157,"@6Sherlockolmes @introvert_hai @SyedNadeemFani Jim Sarbh , a Parsi spoke out against CAA which sought to give relief to poor,unfortunate, harassed, non Muslim refugees from Pakistan, Bangladesh &amp; Afghanistan
INDIA WILL NEVER EVER FORGET
👇 https://t.co/GBQq9SXAiF",set(),0,,"[('SyedNadeemFani', 'PERSON'), ('Jim', 'PERSON'), ('Sarbh', 'PERSON'), ('CAA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Bangladesh', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('INDIA', 'LOCATION')]"
158,@LLCooIH True that but bro we're a poor nation it'd be better if those afghan refugees would have lived their lives here silently but instead they created separatist movements and were involved in many terrorist activities so IM JUST DONE WITH THEIR SHIT FR,set(),0,,[]
159,@pajeetdestroyer We are looking forward now. I think it's fair to say that using refugees as a foreign policy tool WRT Afghanistan was a failure...,set(),0,,"[('WRT', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
160,"“The economic loss is more than twice the total monetary outlay for all the wars the US has fought since September 11, 2001, including those in Afghanistan, Iraq, and Syria.”
via @feeonline 
https://t.co/fSnGNaka3Q",set(),7,,"[('US', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION')]"
161,"Please don't politicize 

Approximately 22 Veteran suicides a day. It's time to change the stigma.

Share these numbers and show our veterans &amp; troops we care and they're not alone. 

Veteran Crisis Line
US 800-273-8255
Press 1
Text 838255 
UK 0800 138 1619
Canada 18334564566 https://t.co/sOEsjuWskr",set(),17,,"[('US', 'LOCATION'), ('Canada', 'LOCATION')]"
162,"2/ Military Crisis line:

1-800-273-8255
Press 1
Text: 838255

Support for deaf and hard of hearing:
1-800-799-4889

Calling from overseas?

In Europe: Call 00800 1273 8255 or DSN 118
In Korea: Call 0808 555 118 or DSN 118
In Afghanistan: Call 00 1 800 273 8255 or DSN 111 https://t.co/5tawdDls25",set(),0,,"[('Europe', 'LOCATION'), ('Korea', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
163,"In today's @UN News in Brief: 

🔸Afghanistan: aid teams deployed to assess impact of fighting 

🔸Progress in tackling #tuberculosis at risk from #COVID19 crisis 

🔸Talks begin to resolve disputed Lebanon-Israel maritime border 

https://t.co/gIPxTzs7rF","{'tuberculosis', 'COVID19'}",2,,"[('UN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('News', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
164,@gremisch Notably many Afghanistan-born girls get shot in the head by terrorists and become a refugee so they can join the Tory party.,set(),0,,[]
165,They turned Afghanistan into hell. Now it's the responsibility of the international community to open its borders for Afghan refugees.,set(),4,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
166,"@AaronCarine @of_axes @Esther_Kahen @elderofziyon @GalGadot And now do take your statement in account for expelled Germans after WW2, Koreans in Korean war,...

The final conclusion in these conversations is always that there're double standards applied when #Israel is in scope.",{'Israel'},0,,"[('Israel', 'LOCATION')]"
167,"@BuzzPatterson good for him, hope he adopts some military-age, single, economic refugee men from Afghanistan, Pakistan, and Syria while he's there",set(),0,,"[('BuzzPatterson', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Syria', 'LOCATION')]"
168,"@MajorPatriot All those years, All those lives, 
the WHOLE Afghanistan War was started because of Obama administration/Clinton LIES!",set(),0,,"[('Obama', 'PERSON')]"
169,"@StoliMark @of_axes @Esther_Kahen @elderofziyon @GalGadot displaced persons returned home after World War II, and refugees returned to Afghanistan and Kosovo. Would you have denied those people the right to return home?",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Kosovo', 'LOCATION')]"
170,"Join Oregon's own @repblumenauer and @AOC for a virtual town hall to discuss the ongoing fight for housing and environmental justice! Tomorrow, October 15th, at 4PM PDT via Zoom! ➡️ Register here: https://t.co/XYCMcA9pFF https://t.co/6dK8P000XB",set(),14,,"[('Oregon', 'LOCATION'), ('AOC', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
171,Voted for gay marriage - War in Afghanistan - war on drugs - an….,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
172,"“I couldn’t believe it’s Europe... which is always talking about human rights.”

Yaser Taheri, who filmed the fire that ravaged the Moria refugee camp in Lesbos, talks to @ggatehouse about how he felt when he first arrived in Moria from Afghanistan

#Newsnight | @refocusmedialab https://t.co/kKaF7pW29w",{'Newsnight'},25,,"[('Europe', 'LOCATION'), ('Yaser', 'PERSON'), ('Taheri', 'PERSON'), ('Moria', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
173,Afghanistan War Exposed: An Imperial Conspiracy https://t.co/mtAV3WqK5u via @YouTube,set(),0,,"[('YouTube', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
174,"So inspiring to see the love shared as part of our @VOSSWater Drops of Kindness campaign. VOSS &amp; I want to surprise you with 10K free VOSS water bottles as a token of our gratitude! And all you have to do - Is Be Kind! 
Click for a chance to win: https://t.co/fHR7kczLnc https://t.co/yj6TuwB0GA",set(),168,,"[('VOSS', 'PERSON'), ('VOSS', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
175,"@TheRock @vosswater I am an autistic former refugee from Afghanistan; entirely self-educated.

Would truly appreciate it if you would read my philosophical essay and re-share.

It covers a range of topics including: poverty, injustices, and the 'why'. Be well.

https://t.co/KL4RY3rrVk",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
176,"@OLCV @repblumenauer @AOC I am an autistic former refugee from Afghanistan; entirely self-educated.

Would truly appreciate it if you would read my philosophical essay and re-share.

It covers a range of topics including: poverty, injustices, and the 'why'. Be well.

https://t.co/KL4RY3rrVk",set(),0,,"[('AOC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
177,@foreverimbetter Bush jr,set(),0,,"[('Bush', 'PERSON')]"
178,@consciousBrOtHa Oh nah I hated his guts. That man got us into the Afghanistan war.,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
179,"Yes @chrislhayes, Kavanaugh, Roberts and Barrett worked on Bush v. Gore 2000 -- along with Ted Cruz. This is a multigenerational movement, and Democrats aren't fighting back hard enough -- and the media isn't covering it. Even those who were there at the time.",set(),916,,"[('Kavanaugh', 'PERSON'), ('Roberts', 'PERSON'), ('Barrett', 'PERSON'), ('Bush', 'PERSON'), ('Gore', 'PERSON'), ('Ted', 'PERSON'), ('Cruz', 'PERSON')]"
180,#Helmand #Afghanistan #TalibanSlaughterHouse #Taliban #Refugees #displacement,"{'Afghanistan', 'Helmand', 'Refugees', 'TalibanSlaughterHouse', 'Taliban', 'displacement'}",1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
181,"#Helmand #Afghanistan #TalibanOccupation #displacement #MassDisplacement
https://t.co/4fLK7PTw4S","{'Afghanistan', 'Helmand', 'displacement', 'TalibanOccupation', 'MassDisplacement'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
182,"🚨🚨🚨🇦🇫#Helmand #Afghanistan #TalibanOccupation #TalibanSlaughterHouse #displacement #MassDisplacement #refugees
https://t.co/tVGmtHwWQ3","{'Afghanistan', 'Helmand', 'refugees', 'TalibanSlaughterHouse', 'displacement', 'TalibanOccupation', 'MassDisplacement'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
183,"What we do know:
1) drone strikes have not gone down and may have increased
2) Trump doesn't care about civilian casualties
3) the Trump administration has censored the reporting of civilian casualties by the US military",set(),0,,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'LOCATION')]"
184,"4) we have actually increased troops in the middle east by 20,000 since 2016
5) we are not withdrawing all troops from Afghanistan despite Trump's claims
6) Trump allowed Russia to bomb &amp; slaughter thousands of Syrian civilians (creating a refugee crisis that destabilized Europe)",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'LOCATION'), ('Europe', 'LOCATION')]"
185,"it is remarkable how little coverage there has been in western media of the Assange trial, where we are witnessing an absolute mockery of justice because a journalist proved beyond any reasonable doubt and with concrete, verifiable proof that the US war machine is criminal.",set(),396,,"[('US', 'LOCATION')]"
186,"@joanwalsh @chrislhayes If Gore had been elected, we could have prevented 9-11 because Gore was aware of the threat; would have avoided wars in Iraq and Afghanistan; would not have relaxed regulations that led to the financial crisis of 2008; would have made a dent in climate change.

187,Afghanistan war hero amputee Ben McBean demands change to blue badge rules https://t.co/j8UiV8BlVR https://t.co/iBKbxBIAr9,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Ben', 'PERSON'), ('McBean', 'PERSON')]"
188,"April 11 2019: Assange arrested, taken out of embassy.

April 12 2019: the ICC declines to investigate American war crimes in Afghanistan, requested by the prosecutor in November 2017, a result of wikileaks' publishing of the Afghanistan war logs.

Related?",set(),0,,"[('Assange', 'PERSON'), ('ICC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
189,"Civilians are routinely killed or injured in armed clashes with high casualties resulting from indirect weapons: mortars, rockets, grenades. These civilians, including many children, must be protected from harm. The only way to do that is to stop the violence. #Afghanistan 4/5",{'Afghanistan'},3,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
190,UNAMA reiterates the urgency to halt violence and to focus on achieving a peaceful negotiated settlement to the #Afghanistan conflict. 5/5,{'Afghanistan'},6,,"[('UNAMA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
191,Violence only heaps further hardship and misery on ordinary #Afghans and undermines efforts for progress and building bridges between parties at the historic #Afghanistan peace talks in #Doha: UNAMA,"{'Afghans', 'Afghanistan', 'Doha'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Doha', 'LOCATION'), ('UNAMA', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
192,"Civilians are routinely killed or injured in armed clashes with high casualties resulting from indirect weapons: mortars, rockets, grenades. These civilians, including many children, must be protected from harm. The only way to do that is to stop the violence: UNAMA",set(),0,,"[('UNAMA', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
193,"UNAMA ""reiterates the urgency to halt violence and to focus on achieving a peaceful negotiated settlement to the #Afghanistan conflict.""",{'Afghanistan'},0,,"[('UNAMA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
194,UNAMA reiterates the urgency to halt violence and to focus on achieving a peaceful negotiated settlement to the #Afghanistan conflict.,{'Afghanistan'},0,,"[('UNAMA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
195,"#DidYouKnow: Most of today's handmade Afghan and Persian rugs and carpets are woven by #AfghanRefugees in Iran and Pakistan. However, Afghan @Refugees don't get the recognition they deserve, since their products aren't labeled as made in #Afghanistan. 

These images come from 🇦🇫. https://t.co/DsBIf9wVbN","{'DidYouKnow', 'Afghanistan', 'AfghanRefugees'}",2,,"[('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
196,@marwilliamson Western media about Uyghurs propaganda is fake and falling https://t.co/OwX9btkE6M,set(),1,,[]
197,"@Xi_Fan @marwilliamson What a travesty when no war criminals were held accountable for the millions of Muslims killed/injured/made refugees in the illegal invasion of Iraq, Afghanistan, regime change. And hundreds of Aborigines death in custody on top of the millions exterminated.",set(),1,,"[('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
198,"@AaronCarine @Raisin13674217 @Scion_of_Zion That claim has always fascinated me for what it says about the Arab residents. 

If they were attached to the land then why did so few fight? There was no shortage of weapons for them to use.

People fight to defend their home, and run when the cause is not theirs.",set(),0,,[]
199,"Save the Children’s Country Director in Afghanistan Christopher Nyamandi said, ""It is deeply concerning that tens of thousands of people, many of them children, have been forced from their homes because of fighting. A humanitarian crisis must be avoided. 
https://t.co/XoPm3www54",set(),2,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Christopher', 'PERSON'), ('Nyamandi', 'PERSON')]"
200,"There is a significant funding gap in the international response to the crisis affecting Rohingya refugees and other displaced Rohingya as well as the communities that host them. On October 22, we join the UK, the EU, and @Refugees to change that dynamic. https://t.co/7JTETLsSDt",set(),127,,"[('Rohingya', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Rohingya', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'LOCATION'), ('EU', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
201,"#PakistanDeserveWhitelist
On the other hand, the challenge of immigrants is very important for the economy of Pakistan, and Islamabad can plan for the return of Afghan refugees by playing a facilitating role and considering its interests in Afghanistan.
@FATFNews
@Arifsawabi https://t.co/NXVgS0tErr",{'PakistanDeserveWhitelist'},11,,"[('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Islamabad', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
202,"[Thread] @hrw has worked w/@unwomenafghan &amp; @UNICEFAfg to document the impact of Covid on girls’ education in Afghanistan. The pandemic has harmed the education of children around the world, especially girls, and nowhere more so than Afghanistan. https://t.co/FqSwn1gChw",set(),27,,"[('Covid', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
203,"@StateDept @Refugees fundraising for Afghan people PLEASE donate.  After 40 years of war, natural disasters &amp; persistent poverty, #COVID19 has thrown Afghanistan into an unprecedented health, social &amp; economic crisis. Despite challenges, people need humanitarian assistant . https://t.co/tKeOWAPpPf",{'COVID19'},0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
204,"Girls' education was in crisis in Afghanistan before the pandemic. The number of girls in school was falling in many provinces, &amp; the gender gap in access to education, between girls &amp; boys was widening again, as violence escalated &amp; donors disengaged.  https://t.co/kxOUOrRI3N",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
205,"Civilians Trapped In Helmand Clashes Worrying Say Amnesty, Save The Children 
#Afghanistan #AmnestyInternational #Helmand #Civilian #Children 
Read more: https://t.co/M6RI2Vm1Ic https://t.co/SxHVFU46sY","{'Afghanistan', 'Helmand', 'Civilian', 'Children', 'AmnestyInternational'}",6,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
206,"@noah_guttman @Raisin13674217 @Scion_of_Zion If people only run when the cause is not theirs, then in Bosnia, Kosovo, Afghanistan, Rwanda and all the other places where wars have produced refugees, we would have to assume that no one was attached to their country. That seems unlikely.",set(),0,,"[('Bosnia', 'LOCATION'), ('Kosovo', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Rwanda', 'LOCATION')]"
207,"Amin Saikal's 'Zones of Crisis: #Afghanistan, #Pakistan, #Iran and #Iraq' sheds light on the shared history of destabilization and sectarian divisions in four Muslim-majority states, writes @KhaledAhmedNW
https://t.co/rT5YvjHF20","{'Afghanistan', 'Iran', 'Iraq', 'Pakistan'}",1,,"[('Amin', 'PERSON'), ('Saikal', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Muslim-majority', 'LOCATION')]"
208,"As always, the most marginalized girls are the most at risk from Covid-19 and school closures.  Girls who are internally displaced, have disabilities, are from ethnic groups facing discrimination and, of course, those who are poor are facing the most harm during the pandemic. https://t.co/QesYizMWbe",set(),1,,[]
209,"""Trapped civilians must be allowed safe passage out of Lashkar Gah"" said #Amnesty International.

@Savethechildren said 1000s of people, many of them children, were forced to flee.

""A humanitarian crisis must be avoided.""

@amnestysasia #Helmand #Taliban #Afghanistan #LashkarGah","{'Afghanistan', 'Helmand', 'Taliban', 'LashkarGah', 'Amnesty'}",7,,"[('Amnesty', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('International', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Savethechildren', 'PERSON'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
210,"Afghanistan is in crisis, but that doesn't mean there are no solutions. There are plenty. 1) Make girls' education a priority in Covid-19 response planning; 2) Do more to end gender-based violence, including child marriage; 3) make equality in education a legal requirement. https://t.co/68LYSNARBK",set(),4,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
211,"#PakistanDeserveWhitelist

Although significant numbers of refugees went to Afghanistan but still millions are living in Pakistan
@Af_tab_ 
@TeamPVFofficial 
@Jzba_e_Pakistan",{'PakistanDeserveWhitelist'},3,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION')]"
212,"575 attacks in Two Weeks: MoIA: Taliban have carried at least 575 offensive attacks throughout Afghanistan in just 2 weeks, inflicting heavy casualties on civilians. 92 mine bombings and six suicide attacks by Taliban among others are carried against civilians and security forces https://t.co/rsOTeNpjJI",set(),0,,"[('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
213,"We @Refugees are on the ground conducting emergency assessments with other humanitarian agencies as tens of thousands are forced to flee their homes and violence in #Helmand #Afghanistan in spite of #COVID19 and the #AfghanPeaceProcess

 https://t.co/PR4gRuxaxC via @AJEnglish","{'Afghanistan', 'AfghanPeaceProcess', 'Helmand', 'COVID19'}",3,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
214,"Each time alliance bombs another hospital, school, market in #Idlib possibly aimed at triggering mass displacement so Syrian army can walk in, retake area w/out a fight in strategy of apparent war crimes that may amount to crimes against humanity  https://t.co/zLJnWM60H1 https://t.co/9HDkZGJOmR",{'Idlib'},5,,[]
215,"#Afghanistan #Hemland #TalibanOffensive #Taliban #TalibanSlaughterHouse #displacement #refugees
https://t.co/BhuRTC9NXx","{'Afghanistan', 'refugees', 'TalibanSlaughterHouse', 'TalibanOffensive', 'Taliban', 'displacement', 'Hemland'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
216,"Huge congratulations to the BBC visual and data journalists who made this powerful piece on the Afghanistan war, that's just won the @RoyalStatSoc Investigative Award: https://t.co/xZZgWEJb0F",set(),0,,"[('BBC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
217,"#Helmand, South-western #Afghanistan #Taliban #TalibanOffensive
https://t.co/1Y3MT7o8aB","{'TalibanOffensive', 'Afghanistan', 'Taliban', 'Helmand'}",0,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
218,"Can we say that the same strategy [war/bombing/violence =&gt; mass displacement =&gt; occupation] has been, and is, being repeatedly employed elsewhere in the world, including #Afghanistan, now, in #LashkarGah, #Helmand, by #Taliban (backed by Russia?).
https://t.co/lNlaJwfKo8","{'Afghanistan', 'Taliban', 'Helmand', 'LashkarGah'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Russia', 'LOCATION')]"
219,"How has #COVID19 impacted #smuggling of #refugees &amp; #migrants from #Afghanistan 

➡️https://t.co/n80CJWZc1k

Nearly half of respondents returned to Afghanistan due to #COVID19 -most citing job losses- economic uncertainty may📈pressure to re-migrate irregularly in search of jobs https://t.co/4lRj9WrFED","{'Afghanistan', 'refugees', 'smuggling', 'migrants', 'COVID19'}",4,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
220,"The ongoing conflict in #Helmand has led to civilian casualties &amp; displacement. @AfghanistanIHRC urges the warring parties to end the conflict immediately, and calls on negotiating teams to agree on a ceasefire. 
https://t.co/Q4qGSETggJ https://t.co/dVp7556JtE",{'Helmand'},5,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION')]"
221,"The Ministry of Refugees and Repatriation (@MoRRAfg):

5,126 families from Nad Ali, Nawa and Nahr-e-Siraj districts, along with Babaji &amp; Bolan districts of Lashkar Gah city have been displaced in #Helmand.

#Afghanistan #Taliban #MoRR https://t.co/W5uGQzdksE","{'Afghanistan', 'Taliban', 'Helmand', 'MoRR'}",3,,"[('Nad', 'LOCATION'), ('Ali', 'LOCATION'), ('Nawa', 'LOCATION'), ('Nahr-e-Siraj', 'LOCATION'), ('Babaji', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('amp', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bolan', 'LOCATION'), ('Lashkar', 'LOCATION'), ('Gah', 'LOCATION'), ('city', 'LOCATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
222,"It's #WorldHandwashingDay! Now, more than ever, this simple act is crucial to saving lives, including in our work supporting refugees' health.

Here are a few of our handwashing stations around the 🌎–from Cameroon, Afghanistan &amp; Thailand–that keep people safe from #COVID19 https://t.co/SxV9vDBjuv","{'COVID19', 'WorldHandwashingDay'}",1,,"[('Cameroon', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
223,"نسیمه نیازی نماینده هلمند:

""زبان #فارسی مربوط به ایران است. زبان مردم افغانستان #دری است که در تمام استانها/ولایات رواج دارد و در قانون اساسی هم‌ نام زبان به صورت واضح دری نوشته شده""
او همچنان از رئیس مجلس میخواهد به کسانیکه فارسی را زبان مادری خود میدانند وقت صحبت کردن ندهد. https://t.co/8kxYTguThj","{'فارسی', 'دری'}",28,,[]
224,"Powerful story of a journalist who's had to run for his life twice, from Afghanistan and now from Iran.
Those refugee boats are full of people with stories like this.
https://t.co/X6IPihrfBd",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION')]"
225,"""Afghanistan's COVID-19 outbreak has pushed another five million people into food shortages, dramatically worsening the humanitarian situation in a country already racked by conflict."" - @benfarmerDT &amp; @akhtar_makoii for @Telegraph 

Full article: https://t.co/EEHItV3BX5",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Telegraph', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Full', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
226,"#TrumpCovidWarDeaths = 216904 and growing.
According to Wiki and Johns Hopkins: 
American Combat deaths:
Korean War 33686 +
Vietnam War 47424 +
Gulf War 149 +
Iraq War 3836 +
Afghanistan War 1833 +
9/11 deaths 2977 
= 89905. 
#TrumpCovidWarDeaths 
= 216904, and growing.",{'TrumpCovidWarDeaths'},0,,"[('Wiki', 'PERSON'), ('Johns', 'PERSON'), ('Hopkins', 'PERSON')]"
227,"1/4 Following several meetings General Miller and I had with the Taliban, we agreed to re-set actions by strictly adhering to implementation of all elements of the U.S.-Taliban Agreement and all commitments made.",set(),135,,"[('Miller', 'PERSON'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
228,Proud to support this ambitious effort to grow and conserve one trillion trees worldwide.🌲🌲🌲,set(),3181,,[]
229,"@US4AfghanPeace Both sides, should take deep consideration to the #Afghans lives. Every day they are killed, tortured and fled. In the recent, #Helmand's crisis is the alive picture of #Afghanistan's situation","{'Afghans', 'Afghanistan', 'Helmand'}",0,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
230,"One of the things I love most about running a news outlet is publishing informed commentaries from readers. This one on the #OpioidEpidemic by Mitch Postich of Rock Hill SC is an excellent example. Our 🎙️ is your 🎙️, people ... https://t.co/cH0DETwKEP",{'OpioidEpidemic'},1,,"[('Mitch', 'PERSON'), ('Postich', 'PERSON'), ('Rock', 'LOCATION'), ('Hill', 'LOCATION'), ('SC', 'LOCATION')]"
231,"@IvankaTrump Fundraising for Afghan people donate small amount for humuatiy.
After 40 years of war, natural disasters &amp; persistent poverty, #COVID19 has thrown Afghanistan into an unprecedented health, social &amp; economic crisis. Despite challenges, people need humanitarian assistant . https://t.co/dv8wBKTLfq",{'COVID19'},0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
232,"Nearly 40,000 people [over 5,600 families] have been displaced in #Helmand, said the provincial Department of Refugees and Repatriation, according to @AP.

#Afghanistan #LashkarGah #Taliban","{'Afghanistan', 'Taliban', 'Helmand', 'LashkarGah'}",3,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Department', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('of', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Refugees', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('AP', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
233,US envoy says Taliban agree to reduce Afghan casualties https://t.co/2XLpt9PqUR #World #Afghanistan #Conflict,"{'World', 'Afghanistan', 'Conflict'}",0,,"[('US', 'LOCATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
234,"Very proud of WFP!!    Nobel Peace Prize: App helps WFP navigate conflict and climate shocks in Afghanistan | by World Food Programme | Oct, 2020 | World Food Programme Insight     https://t.co/kBHHyNt5PL",set(),0,,"[('WFP', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('World', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Food', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Programme', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
235,"@SanSip Good picture, a Sikh sharing a cookie with a Muslim friend. But old one. Now a days Indian Muslims from Kerala blast Sikh Gurudwaras in Afghanistan . Lot of water has flown in river Ganges. A President of European nation said Islam is in crisis . We are not more secular than them",set(),0,,"[('Kerala', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Ganges', 'LOCATION')]"
236,@JohnR1m2o3 @AntoniDYounger @AfghanHistorian It is hard to tell. Leaving may lead to another civil war and civil war will definitely come with the risk of ISIS turning Afghanistan into their safe heaven. Best thing for US now is to leave but extensively and whole heartedly support the Afghan Security Forces,set(),0,,"[('ISIS', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('US', 'LOCATION')]"
237,"The @UN @WFP is on the cutting edge of applying #geospatial analysis toward solving the world food crisis and #ClimateChange in areas like #Afghanistan. Much of what they do is done out of the spotlight, the @NobelPrize is great public recognition of their impact. #GIS #SDGs","{'SDGs', 'ClimateChange', 'Afghanistan', 'geospatial', 'GIS'}",1,,"[('UN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('WFP', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
238,"@KatyJayne101 We could always vote in someone like mass murderers Bliar-Brown and kill hundreds of thousands of innocents in Libya, Syria, Iraq, Yemen, Yugoslavia and Afghanistan. And create millions of refugees.

Then again....maybe not.",set(),0,,"[('Libya', 'LOCATION'), ('Syria', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Yemen', 'LOCATION'), ('Yugoslavia', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
239,"Amid violence in #Helmand, @UNHCRAfg &amp; partners on the ground are reaching out to those in urgent need despite limited access, road closures &amp; telecoms disruptions. We are preparing to distribute emergency aid for the most vulnerable displaced Afghans. https://t.co/mQMIOBJEhA",{'Helmand'},22,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION')]"
240,"Pakistan also suffered massively during the war on terror, but never backed out from its commitment to work closely with Afghan people. Pakistan is hosting refugees and working tirelessly to facilitate the peace process in Afghanistan.
#PakArmyOurPride https://t.co/3cGJNNGtDt",{'PakArmyOurPride'},4,,"[('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
241,"IOM Afghanistan’s Displacement Tracking Matrix collected mobility &amp; needs data and raised #COVID19 awareness, reaching over 62,000 influencers in over 12,300 communities under multi-donor funding from the #GermanForeignOffice. https://t.co/UMl83N7I7R","{'GermanForeignOffice', 'COVID19'}",1,,"[('IOM', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Displacement', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Tracking', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Matrix', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
242,The 20th Year of the Afghanistan War Should Be America’s Last https://t.co/wQ4K6JooVi https://t.co/oFDTJYRGeA,set(),3,,"[('America', 'LOCATION')]"
243,"""#Taliban control roughly 80% of #Helmand province, and over the past year have waged several attacks on #LashkarGah, only to be repulsed by Afghan security forces, whose control is largely restricted to district centers.""
https://t.co/3JmzzgfgmQ","{'Taliban', 'Helmand', 'LashkarGah'}",0,,"[('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
244,@WaliFrozan @AntoniDYounger @AfghanHistorian I think that sounds best. Afghanistan is still in a civil war though whether the US is there or not. One of the problems for the West is that we get refugees who often don't assimilate. A British reporter of Afghan descent talked about how his life was in danger from the,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('West', 'LOCATION')]"
245,"Said Reza Adib is a journalist whose brave investigative reporting has meant he's had to flee his home in Afghanistan, then later Iran. We caught up with Reza in a Greek refugee camp, where he was continuing to ply his trade, in spite of the odds https://t.co/cu2r7pogva",set(),6,,"[('Reza', 'PERSON'), ('Adib', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('Reza', 'PERSON')]"
246,"Forgotten crises: healthcare for #refugees in #Afghanistan
https://t.co/MYejDqGDkq","{'Afghanistan', 'refugees'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
247,whenever Nawaz Sharif feel in crisis Ionian RAW and NSD of Afghanistan increases their attack on our soldiers. The all Nawaz Sharif party jalsa and attacks ratio. Within this weeks there were increased attack on our soldier in Baluchistan and KP border areas by RAW and NSD agents,set(),0,,"[('Nawaz', 'PERSON'), ('Sharif', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Nawaz', 'PERSON'), ('Sharif', 'PERSON'), ('Baluchistan', 'LOCATION')]"
248,"She represents Helmand - a province that’s currently the scene of heavy fighting and mass displacement. 

It’s also one of the poorest provinces in Afghanistan, yet despite all this she decides to focus on superimposing “Dari” onto Persians (even though she isn’t even Persian).",set(),0,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
249,"🚨🇬🇷 In #Greek social networks, rumors are circulating that the Turkish PMC SADAT is recruiting refugees from Syria, Afghanistan &amp; Libya on the island of #Lesbos for transfer to the training camps in Northern Syria to go fight in #Azerbaijan. 200 such persons have been recruited.","{'Greek', 'Azerbaijan', 'Lesbos'}",9,,"[('Syria', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Libya', 'LOCATION'), ('Northern', 'LOCATION'), ('Syria', 'LOCATION'), ('Azerbaijan', 'LOCATION')]"
250,"Sam Power talkin’ about refugee policy and making sure people that worked with the Americans in Iraq and Afghanistan, sure is somethin.",set(),1,,"[('Sam', 'PERSON'), ('Power', 'PERSON'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
251,@edfischman @briebriejoy @BadFaithPod The ‘79 energy crisis won Ronnie the world b/c ppl had to wait in line to fill up their tank.,set(),0,,"[('Ronnie', 'PERSON')]"
252,"@trap_itsa @briebriejoy @BadFaithPod It was a factor. The whole Iran crisis. Afghanistan, Stagflation.

There were political twists, too. Moral Majority helped flip the South. Right-wing supporters of Greater Israel (I refuse to call that Zionism) really hurt Carter in NY, CT and NJ.",set(),0,,"[('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('South', 'LOCATION'), ('Israel', 'LOCATION'), ('Carter', 'PERSON')]"
253,"There are 2.5 million registered refugees from Afghanistan globally, making them the second biggest population of displaced peoples in the world, yet it’s the official policy of many EU countries to forcibly deport Afghans back to Kabul. https://t.co/2G2tsbfEaw",set(),35,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('EU', 'LOCATION'), ('Kabul', 'LOCATION')]"
254,Look how utterly fucking derranged these people are https://t.co/OiPahHQvq2,set(),11,,[]
255,Where to start? Possibly by pointing out that Afghanistan isn't a very LGBT friendly country? Indeed I know one lesbian refugee in the UK whose trans sister also had to flee. Fortunately the sister went to Canada.,set(),2,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('UK', 'LOCATION'), ('Canada', 'LOCATION')]"
256,"8 years ago! It really doesn’t seem that long ago!

Time’s were hard but simple and bonds were made that regardless of the time spent apart today will never be broken.

#ThrowbackThursday #Afghanistan #war https://t.co/oYgpiA0gES","{'ThrowbackThursday', 'Afghanistan', 'war'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
257,"Extraordinary photos of Afghanistan and Australia from ⁦⁦@MuzafAli⁩, a former refugee and tireless advocate for refugee education https://t.co/WedFYtoGzq",set(),1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Australia', 'LOCATION')]"
258,Afghanistan conflict: The families caught in crossfire on Helmand front line https://t.co/r8HHoinxdw,set(),14,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION')]"
259,"""I denounce white supremacy,"" Pres. Trump tells @SavannahGuthrie at #TrumpTownHall. https://t.co/wPfGEhcp8P",{'TrumpTownHall'},98,,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('SavannahGuthrie', 'PERSON')]"
261,"""The only difference this time is that we were ready because we didn't trust the government as much as we did in 2016,"" says Keramullah. ""This time we knew if an attack came, the government couldn't hold out."" https://t.co/cDHHpKFkCa",set(),0,,"[('Keramullah', 'PERSON')]"
262,"Australian Defence Force orders ban on destruction of evidence from Afghanistan war, as inquiry into alleged war crimes nears end - ABC News from ⁦@DanielMOakes⁩  https://t.co/fSPfEZoCgP",set(),1,,"[('Defence', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Force', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
263,Afghanistan conflict: The families caught in crossfire on Helmand front line – #NewsEverything #Asia https://t.co/KS1lh54PNo,"{'Asia', 'NewsEverything'}",0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Asia', 'LOCATION')]"
264,"""Hezb-e-Islami is ready for direct talks with the Taliban, as well as for partnership and cooperation. We believe that if these two groups join hands, the crisis in Afghanistan will end soon and no force will be able to stand against it.""

https://t.co/XSJyVjeKL3",set(),1,,"[('Hezb-e-Islami', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
265,"""We begged them not to shoot us - to let us go and then do whatever you want to each other.""                                      Afghanistan conflict: The families caught in crossfire on Helmand front line https://t.co/853xh9yAsd",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION')]"
266,Afghanistan conflict: The families caught in crossfire on Helmand front line https://t.co/eiDAGUiq2Z https://t.co/zWQfn9sbUi https://t.co/hhOKSXmLcf,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION')]"
267,"It’s really something to see these Aussie posters inside the Grand Courts of the @ArtGalleryofNSW 

I want to thank everyone at AGNSW. While it’s a thrill to see these posters in the gallery, I intend to keep putting them up in the street for as long as I’m able. https://t.co/FRSUSFmyUU",set(),328,,"[('AGNSW', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
268,"Educator Tracey Brown in Kissimmee, FL tells her students “I have a right to dislike blacks” because a gang attacked her. 

 https://t.co/zj35ZAHPLc",set(),456,,"[('Tracey', 'PERSON'), ('Brown', 'PERSON'), ('Kissimmee', 'LOCATION'), ('FL', 'LOCATION')]"
269,"🇦🇫 Congratulations Summia Tora: a refugee, and 2020 graduate of @earlhamcollege who now started postgraduate studies at @UniofOxford as #Afghanistan's 1st Rhodes Scholar! Summia plans to pursue coursework in refugee studies, forced migration, and social entrepreneurship. #GoGirl https://t.co/hCqDBhrxhs","{'Afghanistan', 'GoGirl'}",23,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
270,"Another solid achievement by the BJP government. 

Even Pakistan and Afghanistan handled Covid better than India. https://t.co/C2kILrvWUG",set(),15265,,"[('BJP', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('India', 'LOCATION')]"
271,@notcapnamerica That is so weird because the Taliban tried to kill me in Afghanistan but when I meet refugees from Afghanistan I don't hate them...,set(),0,,"[('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
272,Afghanistan conflict: The families caught in crossfire on Helmand front line https://t.co/p1yapAaajh https://t.co/cIZf0fa6JR,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION')]"
273,Afghanistan conflict: The families caught in crossfire on Helmand front line https://t.co/AKaqxnH7oN https://t.co/Uo4TRgd423,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION')]"
274,"“Life changed into chaos at once”

35,000 lives in fact.  https://t.co/5MdUg6gZRR",set(),1,,[]
275,"Had the BJP govt listened to @RahulGandhi's warning in Feb &amp; taken the Covid crisis seriously, India's covid response wouldn't have been so bad. Under the @INCIndia govt, India's economy competed with China. Under the BJP, even Bangladesh, Pak &amp; Afghanistan are overtaking India!",set(),270,,"[('BJP', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('RahulGandhi', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'LOCATION'), ('India', 'LOCATION'), ('China', 'LOCATION'), ('BJP', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bangladesh', 'LOCATION'), ('Pak', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('India', 'LOCATION')]"
276,"Remembering Liaquat Ali Khan on his death anniversary. He was a statesman, lawyer, political theorist and 1st Prime Minister of Pakistan. He helped and settled 9 million refugees. He was assassinated by Afghan Terrorist Said Akbar after which Pakistan faced many hardships. https://t.co/G6GGNldVGC",set(),303,,"[('Liaquat', 'PERSON'), ('Ali', 'PERSON'), ('Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION')]"
277,"""The socio-economic impacts due to #COVID__19 have been absolutely massive"". The rising needs has led to an additional 3 million people being added into WFP's response in Afghanistan 🇦🇫. Our Dep. Country Director Parvathy Ramaswami spoke to @Telegraph  https://t.co/7J47IYI3h7",{'COVID__19'},5,,"[('WFP', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Parvathy', 'PERSON'), ('Ramaswami', 'PERSON')]"
278,"https://t.co/62hTUtO7CI  Rahul Gandhi slams Centre over COVID-19 handling, says Pakistan, Afghanistan did it better https://t.co/sLjzcSPDWY",set(),0,,"[('Rahul', 'PERSON'), ('Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
279,"MINISTER PAYNE MUST GO OR BE SACKED COVERED UP BIAK ISLAND MASSACRE 6TH JULY documents don't lie   Australian Defence Force orders ban on destruction of evidence from Afghanistan war, as inquiry into alleged war crimes nears end - ABC News https://t.co/2RRCvGAeA2 https://t.co/FVFxWaLah1",set(),1,,"[('PAYNE', 'PERSON'), ('BIAK', 'LOCATION'), ('ISLAND', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('ABC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('News', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
280,"Morrison government lies acts criminally and cover up war crimes by Indonesian military police in West Papua too  Australian Defence Force orders ban on destruction of evidence from Afghanistan war, as inquiry into alleged war crimes nears end - ABC News https://t.co/2RRCvGAeA2",set(),0,,"[('Morrison', 'PERSON'), ('Defence', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Force', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('ABC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('News', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
281,"It's #WorldFoodDay!
Most Europeans think that providing safe and healthy food is a priority, and so do we!
With our #EUGreenDeal &amp; #EUFarm2Fork Strategy, we will:
🚜 Support farmers
🧪 Cut pesticides by 50%
🌾 Increase organic farmed land by 25%
More here: https://t.co/1WTVWzoc8H https://t.co/4eMeTjEMdV","{'WorldFoodDay', 'EUGreenDeal', 'EUFarm2Fork'}",170,,[]
282,"Quite the @UNICEF @Refugees line up!!! 

Had forgotten to share! 

We are proud to work together on our Blueprint for Joint Action to deliver education, Walter &amp;sanitation, and child protection to refugees . 👏 https://t.co/VmqIw10Y9x",set(),5,,"[('UNICEF', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Blueprint', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('for', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Joint', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Action', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Walter', 'PERSON')]"
283,"@EU_Commission After 40 years of war, natural disasters &amp; persistent poverty, #COVID19 has thrown Afghanistan into an unprecedented health, social &amp; economic crisis. Despite challenges, people need humanitarian assistant  fundraising for Afghan children, women https://t.co/rzaig0Qtji",{'COVID19'},0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
284,"@DominiqueHyde @UNICEF @Refugees @LeilaPakkala @CharlottePetriG @jorgeolague @RelanoMeritxell @annika_sandlund After 40 years of war, natural disasters &amp; persistent poverty, #COVID19 has thrown Afghanistan into an unprecedented health, social &amp; economic crisis. Despite challenges, people need humanitarian assistant  fundraising for Afghan children, women. https://t.co/Pa9O4lQpZ4",{'COVID19'},0,,"[('UNICEF', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
285,"Half of Afghanistan’s 30 million people are under 18. They are exposed to extreme situations of violence and abuse due to ongoing fighting, displacement, a poor economy, and harmful social norms and practices.",set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
286,I’m also suspicious of the involvement of @FordFoundation &amp; MacArthur @macfound in the #EndSARSProtest I don’t like to see foreign entities meddling in the internal affairs of my country.  There’s enough potential for trouble in the forthcoming US elections. Why not go there?,{'EndSARSProtest'},25,,"[('MacArthur', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('US', 'LOCATION')]"
287,"Australian Defence Force orders ban on destruction of evidence from Afghanistan war, as inquiry into alleged war crimes nears end via /r/nottheonion https://t.co/PRIHN55BcU https://t.co/uDtpleQ7LX",set(),0,,"[('Defence', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Force', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
288,Very true https://t.co/OcWAILXRw0,set(),1,,[]
289,"@PeterDrewArts @ArtGalleryofNSW Working at Vinnies Migrant &amp; Refugee Centre with a man who came from Afghanistan as refugee a few years ago.

He’s super proud of these posters and the long history of Afghan Aussies.",set(),0,,"[('Vinnies', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Migrant', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('amp', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
290,"Soviet withdrawal from #Afghanistan. 
""In the friendship of peoples is our strength"". 
#USSR
*Notice the missing road wheel.
🇷🇺
#Armor #Afghanistan #war https://t.co/4us3lMnuCa","{'Afghanistan', 'Armor', 'USSR', 'war'}",1,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('USSR', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
291,"@kennels1 Bullshit, Foreign wars and problems don't effect you.
Here's mine.
Born in 1990 
USSR collapses
Yugoslavia Wars
Irag and Afghanistan wars 
08 banks collapses 
refugees crisis
2020 pandemic and economic collapse",set(),0,,"[('USSR', 'LOCATION'), ('Yugoslavia', 'LOCATION'), ('Wars', 'LOCATION'), ('Irag', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
292,"""We just want the war to end. If the government can take control of the area it should run operations so we can return to our homes, but if they can't do that, they should leave the area for the Taliban so we can continue our lives there.”
 https://t.co/dSDby5cULc",set(),1,,"[('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
293,"We're helping build a brighter 💡🔆 future for 150 families in Afghanistan. 

@UNHCRAfg is distributing solar panels - giving people access to their own sustainable energy ⚡️ https://t.co/qqoLJ8urKR",set(),10,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
294,"""They Fight We Die""

I spoke with #Helmand residents caught in crossfires cheated death leaving everything behind just to survive &amp; save their families.

And it is not the first time - thousands of houses, gardens &amp; animals turned in to ashes, once again.

https://t.co/REMGVIg0iH https://t.co/XhrcFrRW8S",{'Helmand'},7,,"[('Helmand', 'LOCATION')]"
295,"No aspect of #Islam left uncontrolled by #China govt, this time on hajj. Endless encroachments on #religiousfreedom, identity, dom and intl #humanrights law. https://t.co/imRxvyGBH0. https://t.co/W2HmzZUdj9","{'Islam', 'religiousfreedom', 'humanrights', 'China'}",35,,"[('China', 'LOCATION')]"
296,"Sunset image ⬆️ is taken by Keramullah a 19 years old resident of Chah-e Anjeer in #Nadali district. He left his car, livestocks and goods in their big garden which is now turned in to a stronghold of ""the #Afghan Army, if not the #Taliban.
Read more here:
https://t.co/REMGVIg0iH","{'Taliban', 'Nadali', 'Afghan'}",1,,"[('Keramullah', 'PERSON'), ('Nadali', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghan', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Army', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
297,"Take an Afghanistan identity card and passport is a big dream for Afghan refugees in Iran
#رویای_بزرگ_برای_مهاجرین_افغان
#کاهش_هزینه_تذکره_پاسپورت_کنسولی https://t.co/RfkpmeqItN","{'کاهش_هزینه_تذکره_پاسپورت_کنسولی', 'رویای_بزرگ_برای_مهاجرین_افغان'}",3,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION')]"
298,"It is deeply concerning to see the devastating impact of #COVID19 in Afghanistan - as livelihoods are destroyed and 5 million people are unable to feed themselves.
 
The country needs urgent support. #WorldFoodDay
https://t.co/lCet3UH09n","{'WorldFoodDay', 'COVID19'}",4,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
299,"Trucks full of Core Relief Items will be dispatched to Lashkar Gah for distribution in #Helmand this afternoon. @UNHCRAfg and partners have started
Protection cash distribution this morning, reaching out to those extremely vulnerable on the ground. More support is needed. https://t.co/Tu1g454hDj",{'Helmand'},11,,"[('Lashkar', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Gah', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION')]"
300,Eradicating corruption and nepotism https://t.co/Oiv1z8cn4c,set(),5,,[]
301,"Adapt,
Survive,
Think Differently

This is the story of #Afghanistan-based CBMHP (IAM) and how they implemented this motto to respond to  #COVID__19. More here 👇in this week's #Covid19StoriesofChange
https://t.co/BpSn0rA0Uk","{'Afghanistan', 'COVID__19', 'Covid19StoriesofChange'}",0,,[]
302,"Thank you LIBERTARIANS. We are getting it all done, and FAST! VOTE TRUMP!!!",set(),14281,,[]
303,"@EagleEye____ @FordFoundation @macfound Foreign intervention, interference &amp;meddling in d affairs of countries like Libya, Somalia, Syria, Yemen, Iraq &amp;Afghanistan have yielded neither peace nor development in those countries. They create refugees &amp; suffering.Those who do not learn from history are doomed to repeat it.",set(),1,,"[('Libya', 'LOCATION'), ('Somalia', 'LOCATION'), ('Syria', 'LOCATION'), ('Yemen', 'LOCATION'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
304,@UNHCRAfg @Refugees @BurenCaroline @unafghanistan @UNHCRgov @mfa_afghanistan @MoRRAfg @UNHCRAsia @OCHAAfg @OCHAAsiaPac @RefugeesMedia Aren't the un just a bunch of criminals,set(),0,,[]
305,"Trumps red wave is the blood of 200k dead Americans. Wait, two hundred and twenty thousand dead Americans now. TWO HUNDRED AND TWENTY THOUSAND.  More than the Korean war, Vietnam war,  first gulf war, iraq war, Afghanistan war all combined. And we've been in Afghanistan 20 years.",set(),0,,"[('Vietnam', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
306,"@phunt72 @Niall001 @Frel_ @nevillebagnall @Muinchille @Ros_Aodha @DefenceIreland @pmakela1 It does, and it’s in NATO.",set(),0,,"[('NATO', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
307,@KeohaneDan @Niall001 @Frel_ @nevillebagnall @Muinchille @Ros_Aodha @DefenceIreland @pmakela1 Exactly and has a crisis management unit that serves in Afghanistan. People from Iceland can also serve in the Norwegian army under a reciprocal arrangement,set(),0,,"[('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Iceland', 'LOCATION')]"
308,"@SkyZamaray @MichaelKugelman why are some jobless afghans so worried and interested in Pakistan, Helmand is under attack, The Americans are leaving, and yet you are more interested in Pakistan?",set(),0,,"[('Pakistan', 'LOCATION'), ('Helmand', 'LOCATION'), ('Pakistan', 'LOCATION')]"
309,@UNHCRAfg @BurenCaroline @RefugeesMedia @MoRRAfg @UNHCRAsia @Refugees @unafghanistan @UNHCRgov @mfa_afghanistan @OCHAAfg @IndrikaRatwatte @UNHCRAfg @BurenCaroline that's great news as because they need it surely...,set(),0,,[]
310,@UNHCRAfg @GulwaliP @BurenCaroline @RefugeesMedia @MoRRAfg @UNHCRAsia @Refugees @unafghanistan @UNHCRgov @mfa_afghanistan @OCHAAfg @IndrikaRatwatte UNHCR needs to sort out rather than providing shelter they don't want this they need to be in their houses because of people Afghanistan is in this situation.,set(),0,,"[('UNHCR', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION')]"
311,@UNHCRAfg @GulwaliP @BurenCaroline @RefugeesMedia @MoRRAfg @UNHCRAsia @Refugees @unafghanistan @UNHCRgov @mfa_afghanistan @OCHAAfg @IndrikaRatwatte We don't want charity we want peace,set(),0,,[]
312,"@fhzadran Pakistan literally host about 3 million official &amp; unofficial Afghan refugees.
